All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece
must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber
after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm going to be the king of the pirates!
The first stop on Luffy's journey is Fishman Island,
thousands of feet below sea level,
where his crew becomes involved in a civil war.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Hordy Jones
and assisted by Vander Decken,
plot to overthrow King Neptune.
The enemy captures Zoro, Usopp, and Brook,
trapping them at the Ryugu Palace,
while the other Straw Hats meet in the sea forest.
Get out of my way!
I gotta go save my friends!
And when I'm done, I'm kicking Hordy's ass!
I told you not to get involved with him!
Something has happened to Hordy!
The true power of the evil drug!
It's time to show the island who's boss!
That's right!
All we gotta do is kill the king!
Once that's done, the royal army will surrender fast!
And if Neptune's dead, Fishman Island's gonna need a new ruler!
I can't wait!
Meanwhile, at Candy Factory Town, in the center of the island...
Bostarama?
Hey, you okay?
He's chewing right through the back three walls!
Yeah, like it was nothing!
My fangs itch for Lloyd!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
What's this crap?
I don't want some trendy cappuccino latte thing or fancy sponge cake when I'm hungry!
That junk's not real food!
What in the hell do I look like?
I'm sorry, boss.
I'll get something else.
That's good, because you're starting to look pretty tasty yourself!
For a snack, I like fish bones, and I like them big!
Now go!
Uh, sure thing.
Big fish bones.
I got it.
Never mind!
I'm gonna go whet my appetite on some soldiers and maybe the royal family, too!
Guess I'll see the rest of you bums at Conchcord Plaza!
Don't you dare be late!
We all have to be there!
What should we do about the citizens?
Come on!
Did you morons pay attention to a word Captain Horty said?
He told us, no more stepping on her picture!
Leave him alone for now!
Those losers will get what's coming to him soon enough!
How are we supposed to stand up to these guys?
Including Horty, the new fish man pirates have four shark fish man as officers!
And a giant squid fish man!
Not to mention their bodyguard is a blue ringed octopus merman known as the best swordsman on the entire island!
I think the Neptune brothers are the only hope we've got left!
And all we can do is keep the faith!
Poor wink!
At Waterwheel town, in the island's northern region!
Did you hear?
The princes are making their way to Conchcord Plaza!
This country's in such a mess!
Tell me about it!
All we wanted to do was improve our relationship with the humans!
There's no reason to threaten everyone with death like some kind of madman!
And on top of those threats, they want to execute the king!
Maybe Horty will be willing to bargain with us!
After all, we've got his men held hostage!
Hmm?
Held hostage?
Your plan isn't going to work!
Boss Horty would rather you cut us Downson than negotiate!
He's more ruthless than the other fish man pirates!
It's why he looks Downson on the rest of us!
This can't be good!
Ever since the princes defeated him, Officer Dosan's power level has dropped to Downson!
Now he's just weak and gloomy!
Let me give him an energy steroid!
Thinking about it just brings me Downson!
It's depressing!
Sometimes Horty makes me frownson!
Horty doesn't like fish men who do business with human pirates!
He'll give them the Bumson without mercy!
Bumson?
All those fish men who donated their blood to help out wounded humans?
He gave them the old Wumson in the dark of night!
Wumson?
Horty believes that human blood is naturally tainted!
And whenever we receive their blood or offer them our own...
We dose in our pure blood under service!
He's back to saying docent now!
Any fish man who supports humans is a traitor and needs to be punished!
Our people will never be able to advance with them in our way!
All right!
That's enough!
I'm gonna go Wumson on you!
He's higher than Dosan!
The chains are shattered!
You bastard!
He knocked them out with one swing!
Fukabushi!
I'll get you back with a slamson!
Then I'll smash your face with a big fat Bumson!
My enemies will face Doomson!
Head to Concord Plaza for the execution!
Let's move!
Yeah!
At the south part of the island, in front of the Fishman Cultural Hall...
Huh?
Uh?
Oh, you call it drunk.
Oh yeah, that's right.
are for the execution let's move at the south part of the island in front of the fishman cultural hall
oh you call it drunk oh yeah that's right it's me this isn't funny anymore boss pull yourself
together you're in no shape to fight like that i think you worry too much pal relax drinks are
on the house it's my street that's not important right now fukaboshi is leading neptune's army
into the plaza we have to be ready for them even worse if things go bad chimbe might even show up to
fight this isn't a joke boss it's no use he's weak as a sea cucumber and just as slippery huh how do you
get your head spinning around like that oh i'm standing still how drunk are you this is awful
i doubt hyozo can even hold his sword sure i can get away from him immediately i'm serious
jozo will slice into anyone and everyone when he's this drunk make a run for it he'll slice anyone
he attacked his own guys
you see i can fight just fine right boys
oh hey yozo why don't you go to the plaza there you can cut up the royal family as much as you want
huh i uh no i uh what is that even supposed to mean
at the marine shopping mall in the east part of the island we're former soldiers of neptune and proud
of it you won't take this country as long as we're around huh what where'd he go
where is he
still he disappeared again damn it did anyone see where he went
you think you pathetic civilians stand a chance you're dumber than i thought
huh bazio can blend in perfectly with his surroundings to camouflage himself
just like a chameleon he might be on our side but even we have trouble figuring out where he is
what this is unfair how are we supposed to fight someone we can't even see you might as well start
begging for the neptune brothers to bail you out without them you're finished though frankly don't
expect them to last long either oh well time to finish you all whoa a roach hurry up kill it
that was weird all of a sudden he stopped talking did we get it is it dead yeah we got it
you fools have nowhere to run it's only a matter of time before we hunt you all down
there's no escaping our wrath he's talking like nothing happened we just beat him to a bump what
class no wonder he's called the noble of the fish man district prepare for the revolution later on
today at conch court plaza the neptune family will die and a new king will rise now let's head to the
the execution what's wrong captain you're not hurt are you don't worry about it you sure i'm fine
just spray me more pills as many as we have but that could kill you we want you to get better but
taking more pills is not the way you're already way over the limit boss
put your head question you fall back in line and shut up captain there's no need for this we already
have king neptune hostage victories right in front of us just give your body a rest listen to us
you're pushing yourself too hard
oh
young
get out of the way jimbae i don't have time for this
I will not! Fishmen problems should be handled by fishmen!
There is no reason why this should be so difficult for you to understand!
Shut up! I don't give a damn about the beef the fishmen and humans have,
especially not when my friends are in danger!
I can rescue your friends! Your interference will do more harm than good!
They both want to help out, so why are they arguing so much?
Their fighting isn't doing any good!
How much longer before we arrive at the plaza?
Less than an hour, sir!
Executing the king at Conchcord Plaza feels calculated!
Why not just do it at the palace?
I think Hordy might be trying to lure you princes into a trap!
That is no concern to me! I look forward to this fight!
I will not let them murder our father!
And I refuse to let our citizens' hearts and minds become closed off after all we've worked for!
Jinbei kept Hordy under his watchful eye, and now I see that we should have taken note of that!
He's probably the reason human pirates have stopped coming here as well, an issue we should have investigated sooner!
Say, do you think Shirahoshi is still in the hardshell tower?
We haven't heard anything about Sis in a while, and it's really starting to bug Mayfasola!
How did you feel about the Straw Hats? Cause I didn't think they were bad people!
Madam Charlie said that they destroyed the country, but so far they seem like the least of our worries!
They have caused their share of trouble, but they may be victims too!
That's what I think! Straw has Jinbei's friend, and the mermaids didn't have a problem with them!
And frankly, their judgment is really wrong!
Agreed, but this is not the time nor the place to ponder such questions!
Right! We need to focus, Solatido!
Summon every soldier that the country has to offer! We're going to save our king at any cost!
Yes, sir!
Merhe!
At Fishfilly Hills, in the northeast part of the island...
It's too tough!
Dammit, we shouldn't be having this much trouble fighting against just one sea monster!
But then again, it seems something is amiss!
Look at these fools! Serves them right!
Alright, Sea King, keep it up!
The energy steroids are making him crazy!
Hey, calm down, Sea Bear! That's enough! The soldiers are barely alive! Our job here is done!
Use this! Sea Kings don't like fire!
Stay back!
What the? I don't think his arms are supposed to bend back like that.
He must be under some kind of a curse.
You idiot!
Put out that fire right away!
Hot, hot, hot!
Huh? You said something about fire?
What are you trying to do? Cook up some smoked squid?
You think we'd eat you?
Oh, the fire.
You were trying to roast me and have me with a glass of sake, he.
When I recover, I'll kill you.
Who'd want to do that? You're crazy!
Oh, sorry, sir.
Careful. I heard about how one of Icarus' best friends was a giant squid.
One day, he swam too close to the sun.
Before you know it, he was a giant dried squid.
That's why Icarus freaks out when he sees fire.
I'm sorry, Dinolos!
But if he's a fish man, he doesn't have anything to worry about.
Dinolos!
No more fire!
Got me here!
Oh, no! That dried squid spear is dangerous.
It turns back into a normal squid by sucking all the fluid out of anyone it strikes.
That guy's as good as jerky!
Icarus!
Wow, that's rough. First he got dried out and then this happened?
Okay, Boss Icarus. I think he's had enough.
Isn't it about time we start making our way to Conchcord Plaza?
We're here.
You're right.
It's too late for that guy. Leave him here.
Minister! You need to see this, sir!
Horty! Is that him up there?
I don't see Horty, but I do see other men from the fish man district!
They must be heading for the Conchcord Plaza!
Damn those bastards!
No way! They still have King Neptune hostage!
You can't let them beat you!
Please do something!
Great knight! Your people need you!
I'm no great knight. Not anymore.
Look at me. I can't even save my poor citizens.
Please hang in there.
What good is a king's army if it can't even protect the king it serves?
We're an embarrassment to this country!
Siricaros! Just two hours left to the execution!
Come with us to Conchcord Plaza!
What happened to Captain Horty? Is he not with you?
Why isn't he talking to me directly here? Huh?
About that.
That drug enhances your strength at the cost of your lifespan.
You shouldn't have taken it in the first place.
Shut up!
Captain Horty was injured!
The human pirate swordsman cut him in the gashes too painful to bear!
Injured? The captain got injured?
His body wouldn't stop hurting so he kept taking energy steroids to help kill the pain!
Now he's messed up!
We told him to stop but he wouldn't listen to anyone!
Oh, Captain Horty!
I can't breathe!
I can't...
I feel like I'm gonna explode!
It's just as I suspected!
The drug side effects are bad enough to kill you!
To kill you!
HUGGHHHGHHHHHHhhh!!!
PURSED
iquing
Whoa, something's wrong.
What's wrong with you now, sea bear?
I think he must be afraid.
But all these sea monsters have been under Captain Horty's control for a really long time now.
I don't know what would spook him so much.
It's at you, Captain!
You doing okay there?
But of course.
And why wouldn't I be?
He's alive, but something changed.
Some of Neptune's soldiers are still alive.
Water shot.
Let's go, Ha!
Honey, terrible!
Neptune's army is crushed by the overwhelming might of the newly transformed Hordi.
The people's last hope lies in the three princes of the Ryugu Kingdom.
Rushing to the scene, they quickly battle Hordi's sea monsters, but his crewmates have a dirty trick up their sleeves that could turn the tables once again.
On the next One Piece, the battle is on at Conchcord Plaza! I'm gonna be king of the pirates!